# SHAHAB HESARAKI

# **Full-Stack Web Developer**

Montreal,Quebec(willing to relocate) +1 (438) 883-9936 Shahabhes@gmail.com Github.com/shahabhesaraki-dev

Motivated full-stack web developer with over three years of learning experience. Expertise in developing, debugging and providing the team with a wide range of suggestions. Fluent in English and Beginner in French.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express.js React.js, Node.js), HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, PHP, Laravel, AWS, Restful APIs, Git, MySQL.

## **EDUCATION**

•	Full-Stack Web Development Diploma (JS - React - Node), Concordia University	2022
•	Professional HTML-CSS Course, McGill University	2021
•	Back-end Development Diploma (PHP-Laravel), Tehran Institute of Technology	2020
•	Front-end Development Diploma (HTML - CSS - JS), Tehran Institute of Technology	2020
•	Bachelor in Management, Technical and Vocational University of Tehran	2014-2018

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Sales Agent, IO Solutions Contact Center Inc. (Canada)

2021-Present

- Establish a climate of trust with the client and analyze them in order to promote products and services.
- Interact with customers by phone, advise and offer solutions adapted to their needs.

# Web Developer (Internship), MehrYasan, Tehran (Iran)

2020-2021

- Writing back-end code and building efficient PHP modules.
- Developing PHP back-end with an optimized MySQL database.

#### IT Technician, ZibaNovin Print, Tehran (Iran)

2015-2019

- Troubleshooting hardware and software issues and supporting network users.
- Installation and upgrading anti-virus software and security systems.

# **RELEVANT PROJECTS**

## **Twitter Clone Project**

A home and profile page based on Twitter. You may send a new tweet and view your friends tweets and retweets. *Technology used:* HTML, CSS, React, Node, Express.is

## **Flight Ticket Project**

A ticket booking application that allows you to reserve a ticket as well as update and delete it. **Technology used:** HTML, CSS, React, Node,, Express.js, MongoDB

#### **Capstone Project**

A fully functional news website that You can send a new post, search for news, leave comments, view related posts, popular posts, and last news. Capable of signing up via email and also logging in with Google.

<u>Technology used:</u> HTML, CSS, React, Node,, Express.js, MongoDB

#### **eCommerce Project**

A watch store that is completely functional. It is possible to add your items to the cart and purchase them and get the confirmation number. Capable of searching for watches, viewing popular models, and selecting sales products. <u>Technology used:</u> HTML, CSS, React, Node,, Express.js, MongoDB